{"description": "This is the Broad Twitter corpus, a dataset of tweets collected over stratified times, places and social uses. \nThe goal is to represent a broad range of activities, giving a dataset more representative of the language used \nin this hardest of social media formats to process. Further, the BTC is annotated for named entities.\n\nFor more details see [https://aclanthology.org/C16-1111/](https://aclanthology.org/C16-1111/)\n", "citation": "@inproceedings{derczynski2016broad,\n  title={Broad twitter corpus: A diverse named entity recognition resource},\n  author={Derczynski, Leon and Bontcheva, Kalina and Roberts, Ian},\n  booktitle={Proceedings of COLING 2016, the 26th International Conference on Computational Linguistics: Technical Papers},\n  pages={1169--1179},\n  year={2016}\n}\n", "homepage": "https://aclanthology.org/C16-1111/", "license": "", "features": {"id": {"dtype": "string", "_type": "Value"}, "tokens": {"feature": {"dtype": "string", "_type": "Value"}, "_type": "Sequence"}, "ner_tags": {"feature": {"names": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "_type": "ClassLabel"}, "_type": "Sequence"}}, "builder_name": "parquet", "dataset_name": "broad_twitter_corpus", "config_name": "broad-twitter-corpus", "version": "1.0.0", "splits": {"train": {"name": "train", "num_bytes": 1532753, "num_examples": 5342, "dataset_name": "broad_twitter_corpus"}, "validation": {"name": "validation", "num_bytes": 517845, "num_examples": 2002, "dataset_name": "broad_twitter_corpus"}, "test": {"name": "test", "num_bytes": 625972, "num_examples": 2002, "dataset_name": "broad_twitter_corpus"}}, "download_checksums": {"hf://datasets/GateNLP/broad_twitter_corpus@20dedb45cd2d6e45b8f41d5e18a0aea0d240d570/broad-twitter-corpus/train/0000.parquet": {"num_bytes": 448923, "checksum": null}, "hf://datasets/GateNLP/broad_twitter_corpus@20dedb45cd2d6e45b8f41d5e18a0aea0d240d570/broad-twitter-corpus/validation/0000.parquet": {"num_bytes": 162851, "checksum": null}, "hf://datasets/GateNLP/broad_twitter_corpus@20dedb45cd2d6e45b8f41d5e18a0aea0d240d570/broad-twitter-corpus/test/0000.parquet": {"num_bytes": 191737, "checksum": null}}, "download_size": 803511, "dataset_size": 2676570, "size_in_bytes": 3480081}